https://anad.org/privacy-policy-disclaimer-terms-of-use/

Privacy Policy
We are committed to honoring your privacy and providing you with the highest level of protection of any personal information you choose to share with us. We understand how important privacy is to each of our members but the internet is a public place. We will not distribute or sell information to any 3rd party. We also are in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.
ANAD does not transmit or input any Protected Health Information as defined by HIPPA privacy regulations through this Site. If you have transmitted any medical information or believe there to be a breach of HIPAA please contact us at .
By contacting us, we reserve the right to contact you through the mediums you have provided. Additionally, if your Personal Information changes, you no longer desire to be contacted directly, or you no longer wish to use or access one of ANAD’s Sites or services, we encourage you to correct, update or remove the Personal Information the next time we email or call you. You may also contact us at
or 630-577-1333.
We take precautions to protect your information. Security of Personal Information is protected by secure server software (SSL) for our email accounts and operating systems to prevent theft. Donations on this Site are collected through PayPal, WePay. Financial data you input to consummate a transaction is encrypted using SSL technology and only the actual credit card processors receive your credit card number. ANAD does not gain access to or see your credit card number. All information collected via credit card and debit card transactions are subject to the privacy policies of PayPal, Inc. and their partner internet payment service providers.
We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we advise you otherwise. Your continued use, interaction with, participation in, or visit of any ANAD owned Site, property or event after this Privacy Policy has been amended shall be deemed to be your continued acceptance of the provisions of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to bookmark this Web page and review it regularly.
Contact:
Telephone: 630-577-1333
Email:
Mail: 220 N. Green Street
Chicago IL 60607
We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we advise you otherwise.
This Privacy Policy was last changed on May 1, 2019.
Treatment Directory Disclaimer
The aim of this ANAD online directory is to provide individuals seeking help with an eating disorder the names of professionals who feel they can provide guidance and help to these individuals. Professional organizations are therefore included in this directory.
Although all due care is taken to ensure accuracy and timeliness of the information, ANAD and its agents are NOT responsible for the accuracy of the information or for any errors or omissions in this directory however caused or for any consequential loss or damage caused to third parties. Information is provided on the basis that all persons accessing this directory undertake responsibility for assessing the relevance and accuracy of its content.
Inclusion of any name or organization does not imply any endorsement by ANAD of any services or products of the names listed.
The names or organization listed in the database have stated to ANAD that:
They have not engaged in non-discriminatory or legal activity
Have expertise in the area of eating disorders
Terms of Use
Access and/or use of www.anad.org (the “Website”) constitutes express acceptance of this ANAD Terms of Use Agreement and ANAD’s Privacy Policy.
The National Association for Anorexia Nervosa and Associated Disorders does not give medical or treatment advice and is not a substitute for medical or psychological treatment. We urge you to speak with your physician and qualified health provider regarding your symptoms and treatment. ANAD does not endorse or recommend any products, sites, treatment centers, service providers, forms of treatment, or research studies.  The consumer is responsible for interviewing and selecting a suitable provider. Professional members who are on the referral list have requested to be listed.
Referral information is supplied solely by the facilities and providers. As a benefit of joining ANAD and paying annual dues, a provider may be placed on the referral list. ANAD does not screen or evaluate the providers and does not verify the credentials or licensing of any of the listed providers or group facilitators.
Intellectual property, including copyrights, patents, trademarks and other property or proprietary rights (registered and unregistered), located in and on this Website are owned or licensed by ANAD, or otherwise used by ANAD as permitted by applicable law. ANAD reserves all of its rights to the content generated on this Website. To the maximum extent permitted under law, all text, images, downloadable files and other materials available on the Website are protected. Nothing in these Terms grant you a right or license to use any trademark, design right or copyright owned or controlled by ANAD or any other third party.
You agree to use this Website and any ANAD content only for lawful purposes, and in a manner which does not infringe the rights of, or restrict or inhibit the use and enjoyment of this Website and any ANAD content by any third party. Such restriction or inhibition includes, without limitation, conduct which is unlawful, or which may harass or cause distress or inconvenience to any person and the transmission of obscene or offensive content or disruption of normal flow of dialogue within this Website.
ANAD reserves the right to terminate your access to the Website at any time, without prior notice or liability for any reason, including without limitation if you violate any provisions of these Terms of Use.
ANAD has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for any third party websites linked from this Website and any visit to a third party website linked from this Website is voluntary and you are responsible for reading the individual Terms and Conditions Policies for any such website.
Donations made through this website are made through PayPal, Inc. and their affiliated internet payment service providers, which are not affiliated, related to, or overseen by ANAD. All donations are subject to the privacy policies of PayPal, Inc. and their affiliated internet payment service providers.
YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” WITHOUT EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND. YOU USE ANAD CONTENT AND THIS WEBSITE AT YOUR OWN RISK. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, ANAD , AND ALL OWNERS OF THE CONTENT MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS AND DISCLAIM ANY WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF SATISFACTORY QUALITY, MERCHANTIBILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT.
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL ANAD BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, ACTUAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES ATTRIBUTABLE TO ANY LOSS OF DATA, LOSS OF BUSINESS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROFITS, OR LOSS OF USE, ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE MATERIALS OR INFORMATION ON THIS WEBSITE (OR WEBSITES LINKED TO THE SITE), EVEN IF ANAD HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY APPLIES TO ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY CAUSED BY, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECT, DELAY IN MAIL OR OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, COMMUNICATION LINE OR INTERNET SERVICE FAILURE, THEFT OR DESTRUCTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO, ALTERATION OF, OR USE OF RECORD, WHETHER FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORTIOUS BEHAVIOR, STRICT LIABILITY, NEGLIGENCE, OR ANY OTHER CAUSE OF ACTION. THIS DOES NOT AFFECT YOUR STATUTORY RIGHTS AS A CONSUMER.
To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to indemnify and hold ANAD harmless from and against all damages, losses, and expenses of any kind (including reasonable attorney fees and costs) arising out of any of the following but not limited to: your breach of these Terms of Use, any activity in which you engage on or through this Website, and your violation of any law or the rights of a third party.
These Terms of Use and any disputes regarding the operation and effect of the provisions of these Terms of Use shall be decided in accordance with the laws of the United States of America (where applicable) and the State of Illinois.
FURTHERMORE, SHOULD ANAD BE SUCCESSFUL IN ANY DISPUTE ARISING FROM THESE TERMS, YOU WILL BE LIABLE FOR ANY EXPENSES RELATED TO THE DISPUTE, INCLUDING REASONABLE ATTORNEYS FEES AND COSTS.
Other than stated in these Terms of Use or as explicitly agreed upon in writing between you and ANAD, the content of these Terms of Use constitutes the entirety of the Terms of Use agreed upon between you and ANAD and supersedes any prior agreements in relation to the subject matter of these Terms of Use.
Unless otherwise stated in these Terms of Use, should any provision be held invalid or unenforceable for any reason or to any extent, such invalidity or enforceability shall not in any manner affect or render invalid or unenforceable the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use, and the application of that provision shall be enforced to the extent permitted under the law. Any failure by ANAD or any third party beneficiary to enforce these Terms of Use or any provision of, shall not waive ANAD’s or the third party beneficiary’s right to do so.
We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of these Terms of Use at any time and without prior notice, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we advise you otherwise. Your continued use, interaction with, participation in, or visit of any ANAD owned Site, property or event after these Terms of Use have been amended shall be deemed to be your continued acceptance of the provisions of these Terms of Use. We encourage you to bookmark this Web page and review it regularly.
Contact:
Telephone: 630-577-1333
Email:
Mail: 220 N. Green Street
Chicago IL 60607
We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of these Terms of Use at any time and without prior notice, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we advise you otherwise.
These Terms of Use were last changed on May 1, 2019.
ANAD is a registered 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization (EIN 36-2938021)
You can also support ANAD by setting us as your Amazon Smile Charity!
© 2020 National Association of Anorexia Nervosa and Associated Disorders.
